Democratic Study Group Records
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part I: Subject File, 1940-1975 (Box I:42-73)
  - Bureau of the Budget Library, 1963-1964
  - CBS Television Network, “Selling of the Pentagon,” 1971
  - Congressional Quarterly, story on the DSG, 1960
  - Calendar Wednesday, 1960-1961
  - Candidates
    - Defeated in primaries, 1964
    - Letters of appreciation, 1961-1971, (2 folders)
    - Requests, 1970 (Box I:43)
  - Civil rights
    - Act, 1963-1965, (3 folders)
    - Legislation, 1957-1962
    - Miscellany, 1960-1970, (4 folders); (1 folder) (Box I:44)
    - Questionnaire, 1963
    - Steering Committee, 1965-1966, (2 folders)
  - Congressional
    - Ethics, 1966-1967
    - Newsletters and press releases
      - Miscellany, 1959-1968, (3 folders)
      - Staebler, Neil, 1964
      - Thompson, Frank, 1964
      - Congressional Record, 1965
  - Congressional reorganization
    - Joint Committee on the Organization of Congress, 1965
    - Miscellany, 1960-1972, (3 folders) (Box I:45)
  - Constitutional amendment on reapportionment
    - Graham, Thomas D., 1964-1965
    - Hansen, John, survey, 1965
    - Miscellany, 1956-1967, (5 folders); (2 folders) (Box I:46)
    - News clippings, 1962-1967, (8 folders)
    - Printed matter, 1940, 1958, 1964-1967, (2 folders); (5 folders) (Box I:47)
  - Contributors to DSG, 1960-1966
  - Defense, 1958-1969, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box I:48)
  - Democratic Caucus
    - Correspondence, 1967-1972
    - Disciplining Representatives Albert W. Watson and John Bell Williams, 1960-1967
    - News clippings, 1962
  - Democratic National Committee, 1960-1965
  - Democratic Party chairmen, 1969
  - Distribution of funds to members, 1960
  - District of Columbia
    - Home Rule Steering Committee, 1965-1966
    - Miscellany, 1965-1969
  - Economy, 1963-1972
  - Education, 1964-1970
  - Election of officers, 1960-1967, (2 folders)
  - Electoral College, 1966-1969, (1 folder) (Box I:49)
  - Emergency Detention Act of 1950, 1971
  - Employment, 1962-1974, 1984
  - Environment, 1960-1970
  - Executive committee, 1959-1968, (5 folders)
  - Executive departments and agencies, 1964
  - February second dinner, New York, N.Y., 1964
  - Federal, state and local government relations, 1961-1964
  - “Federal Benefits & Outlays & Tax Contributions” for congressional districts in 1971, computer printouts See Oversize
  - Foreign Policy Steering Committee, 1960-1966
  - Full Employment Steering Committee, 1965-1966 (Box I:50)
  - Functions (DSG), 1970
  - Fund-raising, 1962-1967, (8 folders); (3 folders) (Box I:51)
  - General correspondence, 1959-1972, (5 folders); (6 folders); (8 folders) (Box I:52, Box I:53)
  - Government publications distributed by DSG, 1964 (Box I:54)
  - Group Research, Inc., 1964-1968
  - Harriman-Clark appeal letter, 1970
  - House Rules Committee
    - Miscellany, 1948-1966, (6 folders); (7 folders) (Box I:55)
    - News clippings, 1952-1967, (8 folders) (Box I:56)
  - Housing, 1963
  - Immigration, 1965
  - Information about DSG, 1959-1973
  - Invitations, 1964
  - The Johnson Administration..., 1965
  - Joint luncheons, undated
  - Kennedy, John F., position papers, 1960
  - Krauss, Lawrence G., 1964 (Box I:57)
  - Kravchenko, Valery, visit to DSG office, 1961
  - Labor, 1964
  - Legislation, 1954-1971, (2 folders)
  - Letters of appreciation
    - From DSG, 1967-1973
    - To DSG, 1970-1973
  - Liberal Project, 1957-1962
  - Lists
    - African-American press, undated
    - Democratic Study Group
      - Executive committee, 1960
      - Financial, 1966-1967
      - Mailing lists, 1960-1961, 1969-1973, (2 folders)
      - Members of Congress, 1960 (Box I:58)
      - Membership, 1959
      - Miscellany, 1961-1963, (2 folders)
      - Plates, commemorative, 1960
      - Press, 1960
      - State districts, undated
      - Whip, 1960
    - Finance committee publications, 1960
  - Luncheon Club, 1957-1963, 1972, undated
  - Mail log, undated
  - Mailings to members, 1960-1971, (5 folders)
  - Materials and publications, 1969-1973, (5 folders) (Box I:59)
  - Medicare and health, 1965
  - Meetings, 1959-1965
  - Members' correspondence, 1960-1969
  - Members from marginal districts, 1958
  - Membership address forms, 1959
  - Midstream, evaluation of DSG by DSG, 1960
  - Midwest conference, 1964 (Box I:60)
  - Migratory labor, 1960-1961
  - Miscellany, 1956-1974, (2 folders)
  - Mississippi challenge, Democratic Party convention (1964)
    - Miscellany, 1959-1965, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box I:61)
    - News clippings, 1965
    - Questionnaire, 1965
  - Mississippi Freedom Democratic Party, 1965
  - Moss, John E., letter to Labor Secretary James P. Mitchell, 1960
  - National Committee for an Effective Congress, 1957-1966, (2 folders)
  - New member to Congress orientation, 1964-1965
  - News clippings, 1955-1969, (1 folder); (10 folders) (Box I:62, Box I:63)
  - Nixon administration, DSG report, 1972
  - Nutrition, 1970-1971
  - Office procedure, 1964
  - Okun, Arthur, meeting with DSG members, 1968
  - One hundred dollar contributors, 1970-1971
  - Organizations, 1964
  - Outside mailings, 1966
  - Overview of DSG, circa 1966
  - Phillips, William G.
    - “A New Party for the South,” 1957-1958
    - Personal correspondence, 1955, 1962-1965
  - Photographs, 1966-1968, undated
  - President's Club of New York, 1966 (Box I:64)
  - Press releases, 1956-1972
  - Printed matter, 1941, 1952-1969, (3 folders)
  - Projects, 1959
  - Public relations media firms, 1964
  - Publications (including planned), 1964
  - Publications by DSG, utilization of, 1970
  - Radio usage, 1962 (Box I:65)
  - Reception for new members of Congress, 1964-1967
  - Re-election seminars, 1965-1966, (2 folders)
  - Regulatory agencies, 1959-1964
  - Replies to members of Congress, 1973
  - Requests, 1963-1973
  - Research material, 1959
  - Right-wing related material, 1957, 1965-1966
  - “Round-Robin” letters, 1968
  - School prayer decision, 1963-1964 (Box I:66)
  - Science and research, 1963-1964
  - Secrecy, 1970-1971
  - Services for DSG, 1970-1973, undated
  - Social hours, 1971
  - Social security and medicare, 1962-1972, undated
  - Special correspondence, 1959-1972, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box I:67)
  - State political organizations and committeemen, 1964
  - Staff
    - Christmas party, 1966
    - Miscellany, 1964-1973
    - Roundtables, 1966
  - Student correspondence, 1963-1964
  - Study room, 1960-1961
  - Suggestions, 1970
  - Summer interns, 1962-1972, (5 folders)
  - Supreme Court, 1957, 1963-1964
  - Taft-Hartley Act, repeal of section 14(b), 1952, 1965
  - Tarnofsky, Ivan de, 1963-1964 (Box I:68)
  - Task forces (DSG)
    - Appropriations, 1971
    - Assignments, 1960
    - Civil Rights, 1960-1971
    - Communications, 1970-1971
    - Congressional Reorganization and Reform, 1969-1971
    - Consumer, 1969-1971
    - Economic and Tax Policy, 1969-1972
    - Education and Manpower, 1969-1970
    - Foreign Policy, 1967-1972, (3 folders)
    - Health and Welfare, 1969-1971
    - International Affairs and Defense Policy, 1969-1971
    - Law Enforcement and Constitutional Rights, 1969-1970
    - Miscellany, 1969-1971
    - Questionnaire, 1960 (Box I:69)
    - Urban Affairs, 1967-1970
  - Tax questionnaire, members of Congress, undated
  - Taxation, 1949-1969
  - Television
    - Miscellany, 1964-1971, undated
    - Scripts (DSG), 1964
  - U-2 incident, 1960
  - United Auto Workers, 1965-1970
  - University correspondents, 1964
  - Urban affairs, 1965
  - Volunteers, 1970
  - Vote books, 1972
  - Voting patterns in the House of Representatives, 1969
  - Voting Rights Bill of 1965, 1964-1965, (4 folders) (Box I:70)
  - Wheat sales to Russia, 1962-1964
  - Whip (DSG)
    - Calls, 1960, 1967-1972, (3 folders); (4 folders) (Box I:71)
    - Notices, 1967-1970, (4 folders)
    - System, 1960-1972, (4 folders)
  - White House
    - Miscellany, 1964
    - Press releases, 1964-1965, (7 folders); (2 folders) (Box I:72, Box I:73)
- Part I: Printed Matter, 1953-1971 (Box I:73-74)
  Pamphlets, booklets, reports, and related material.
  - 1953-1968, (4 folders) (Box I:73)
  - 1968-1971, (3 folders) (Box I:74)
- Part I: Oversize, 1971-1972 (Box I:OV 1-OV 2)
  Federal benefit data for congressional districts.
  Arranged and described according to the series and folders from which the items were removed.
  - “Federal Benefits & Outlays & Tax Contributions” for congressional districts in 1971, computer printouts (Container I:49) (Box I:OV 1)
    - Alabama-New Mexico
    - New Mexico-Wyoming (Box I:OV 2)
- Part II: Administrative File, 1939-1995 (Box II:1-36)
  Bylaws, election results, committee records, financial and personnel records, legal documents, correspondence, reports, studies, surveys, promotional material, news clippings and scrapbooks.
  - Academic studies and history For additional material see Containers II:29-34, Scrapbooks (Box II:1)
    - Bibliographies, 1965-1973
    - Chronological file, 1959-1989, (5 folders)
    - “The Democratic Study Group: A Party within a Party,” 1970
    - “The Democratic Study Group: A Study of Intra-Party Organization in the House of Representatives,” 1964
    - “The Democratic Study Group: An Appraisal,” 1970 (Box II:2)
    - “Mobilization of Liberal Struggle in the House, 1955-1970: A Look at the Democratic Study Group,” 1971
  - Attacks on DSG
    - Bailey, Wendell, 1979-1981
    - Republican Congressional Campaign Committee, 1976-1979
  - Bill Phillips Recognition Fund, 1967
  - Brochures, resolutions, and statements on activities and services, 1962-1965, 1976-1977, undated
  - Brodhead, William M., 1982
  - Burton, Philip
    - Death, 1983
    - House of Representatives election, 1982
    - Miscellany, 1974-1975, 1981-1983, undated
  - Bylaws
    - 1962-1981
    - 1993, undated
  - Conlon, Richard P.
    - Democratic Caucus study, “Responsible Party Model,” 1973
    - Interviews, 1971-1975
    - Kennedy, Edward M., 1980-1981 (Box II:3)
    - Miscellany, circa 1964, 1976-1987
    - “A New Problem in Campaign Financing, and a Simple Legislative Solution,” 1984-1985
    - Speaking engagements, 1981
  - Correspondence
    - 1966-1990, (2 folders)
    - 1993-1995
  - Distinguished service awards, 1965-1967
  - Election of officers
    - 1962-1971, (4 folders)
    - 1973-1989, (10 folders) (Box II:4)
    - 1991-1994, (3 folders)
  - Employment (Box II:5)
    - Application form, undated
    - Hired, 1959-1967, undated, (7 folders)
    - Letters of application, 1966-1984, (4 folders)
    - Not hired, 1961-1965, (5 folders)
    - Résumés, 1957-1990, (1 folder) (Box II:6)
  - Executive committee
    - Chairmen and committee appointments, 1965, 1989
    - Chronological file
      - 1967-1990, (2 folders)
      - 1993
    - Meetings
      - 1968-1976, (6 folders)
      - 1977-1983, (8 folders) (Box II:7)
      - 1984-1990, (8 folders) (Box II:8)
      - 1991-1992, (2 folders)
      - 1993-1995, undated (Box II:9)
    - Photographs, undated
    - Policy positions, 1977, undated
    - Rosters
      - 1975-1988
      - 1989-1994, undated
  - Federal Election Commission complaint, 1972, 1980-1982
  - Finances
    - Account book, 1969-1973
    - Bank statements
      - 1963-1969, (1 folder)
      - 1970-1982, (1 folder) (Box II:10)
    - Billings, 1979
    - Campaign funding
      - DSG 1964 Campaign Fund, 1964
      - DSG 1966 Campaign Fund, 1966-1968
      - DSG 1968 Campaign Fund, 1968-1970
      - DSG 1970 Campaign Fund, 1970-1971
      - Miscellaneous campaign funds, 1971-1980, undated
    - Checks issued
      - 1971-1974, (1 folder)
      - 1974-1981, (3 folders) (Box II:11)
    - Chronological file
      - 1966-1969, 1976-1989, (3 folders)
      - 1990-1994, undated
    - Clerk hire, 1971-1988, undated
    - Contributions received, 1960, 1968, 1976-1982, (2 folders) (Box II:12)
    - Dues paying members, 1965-1980, (8 folders)
    - Expenses
      - Coffee and tea, 1989-1990
      - Computers, 1989-1990, (2 folders)
      - Democratic Club, 1989-1990
      - Equipment purchase, 1989-1990 (Box II:13)
      - Equipment rental, 1989-1990, (2 folders)
      - House restaurant, 1989-1990
      - Insurance, 1990
      - Late work expenses, 1989-1990
      - Messenger service, 1989-1990
      - Miscellaneous, 1989-1990
      - New member orientation, 1989-1990
      - Office supply service
        - 1989, (1 folder) (Box II:14)
        - 1990, (2 folders)
      - Paper, 1989-1990
      - Postage, 1989-1990
      - Printing, 1989-1990
      - Production supplies, 1989-1990
      - Research assistance, 1989-1990
      - Subscriptions and publications, 1989-1990
      - Taxes, 1989-1990
      - Telephone, 1988-1990, (4 folders) (Box II:15)
    - Federal unemployment tax return, 1986
    - Financial projections, 1983
    - Fund raising
      - Chronological file, 1964-1987, undated, (5 folders)
      - Constituent responses, 1981-1983 (Box II:16)
      - Contact lists, 1971, undated
      - Direct mailings and mailing data, 1970-1972, 1983-1984, (3 folders)
      - Events
        - Anniversaries
          - Tenth, 1969-1970, (2 folders)
          - Twelfth, 1971
          - Fourteenth, 1973
          - Twenty-fifth, 1984
          - Thirtieth, 1989
        - Commemorative dinner, 1986
        - Democratic Party convention, New York, N.Y., 1976
        - O'Neill, Thomas P., dinner for the speaker, 1977-1979
        - Pepper, Claude, dinner, 1939, 1982, undated
        - Presidential dinner for Jimmy Carter, 1976 (Box II:17)
    - Payments received
      - 1976-1989, (6 folders)
      - 1989-1993 (Box II:18)
    - Publication orders, 1983
    - Subscription fees, 1977-1988
    - Tax status, legal review, 1980-1981 See Container II:36, same heading
    - Telephone billing change, 1984
  - Handbook, 1977
  - History See Container II:1, Academic studies and history
  - IBM Magnetic II typewriter, 1976-1980
  - Invitations, 1980-1982
  - Job referral service
    - Announcements, 1986-1988
    - Establishment, 1970, 1979, undated
    - Lists of selected “order,” 1983-1984
    - Number guides
      - 1984-1985, (1 folder)
      - 1986-1988, undated, (4 folder) (Box II:19)
  - Legislative service organizations
    - Compliance
      - Attestors
        - 1984-1990, (2 folders)
        - 1992
      - Certification request, 1993-1994
      - Chronological file
        - 1973-1977, (4 folders)
        - 1979-1990, (7 folders) (Box II:20)
        - 1991-1992, (2 folders)
        - 1993-1994, undated, (3 folders) (Box II:21)
    - Financing
      - Miscellany, 1980-1984
      - Profile, 1984
      - Reports
        - Democratic Study Group
          - 1979-1986, (3 folders)
          - 1987-1990, (3 folders) (Box II:22)
          - 1991-1995
        - Other congressional support organizations, 1982-1984
    - House Task Force on Legislative Service Organizations
      - Intent to operate as legislative service organization, 1981
      - Miscellany, 1981-1988, (2 folders)
      - Obey Commission, 1977 (Box II:23)
      - Proposed regulations, 1977-1983, undated, (3 folders)
      - Questionnaire, 1982-1984
      - Regulations
        - 1976-1982, 1990
        - 1992-1993, undated
      - Tax question, 1978-1981
  - “Liberal Manifesto,” 1957
  - Liberal project, 1986
  - Library of Congress, 1972-1986 (Box II:24)
  - Meeting notices and agenda, 1964-1987, (7 folders)
  - Members, subscribers, and participants
    - Mailing lists, 1985
    - Members
      - 1959, (1 folder)
      - 1965-1979, undated, (11 folders) (Box II:25)
    - Miscellaneous, 1965-1989, undated
    - Room and phone numbers, 1991, undated (Box II:26)
  - News clippings For additional material see Containers II:29-34, Scrapbooks
    - 1959, 1965-1990, (3 folders)
    - 1991-1992, (2 folders)
  - Newsletter proposals
    - “DSG Report,” 1981-1982
    - “News Notes,” 1981
    - “Pioneer,” 1977-1981
  - Notebooks, 1977
  - Notes and miscellany, 1964-1972, 1987, undated
  - Office management
    - 1966-1977, (4 folders)
    - 1978-1988, undated, (5 folders) (Box II:27)
  - Office space, 1967-1978, undated
  - Phillips, William G., 1962-1970
  - Plaques awarded, 1974-1992
  - Polling
    - Chronological file, 1974-1985, undated, (8 folders)
    - Cooper, David, 1975-1978
    - Mann, Thomas E., 1974-1978
  - Press contacts, 1989, undated
  - “Public Opinion Roundup,” 1981-1985 (Box II:28)
  - Publications, style and format, 1975- 1982, undated
  - Questionnaires See also Containers II:34-36, Survey research
    - Campaign practice arbitration rules, 1967
    - Committee staff, 1981
    - Congressional reform, 1970
    - Democratic Study Group role, 1978
    - Evaluation of DSG research services, 1977
    - Mailing instructions, undated
    - Rules committee, 1966
  - Reorganization proposals
    - Regions, 1977
    - Relocation, 1975-1977
    - Structural changes, 1965, 1971
    - Termination, 1994
  - Research output, 1968-1983
  - Research services, 1970-1985, undated (Box II:29)
  - Retirement party, 94th Congress, 1976
  - Room reservations, 1975-1979, undated
  - Sabo, Martin Olav, 1985-1991
  - “Save the Capitol” campaign, 1966
  - Schroeder, Patricia, criticism of Democratic Study Group, 1983
  - Scrapbooks
    - “DSG as a Group,” 1960-1969, (2 folders)
    - “DSG Organization and Personnel,” 1959-1971
      - Vol. 1, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:30)
      - Vol. 2, (3 folders)
    - “Origins and Early Activities... ,” 1957-1969, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box II:31)
    - “Press Clippings,” 1970-1981
      - Vol. 1, (2 folders)
      - Vol. 2 (Box II:32)
      - Vol. 3, (2 folders)
      - Vol. 4, (1 folder) (Box II:33)
    - “Research and Legislative Activities,” 1957-1970
      - Vol. 1, (3 folders)
      - Vol. 2, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:34)
      - Vol. 3
  - Social hour, 1971
  - Staff
    - Ford, Carolyn, 1989
    - Conlon, Richard P. See Containers II:2-3, same heading
    - Interns, 1966-1988
    - Miscellany, 1966, 1979-1981
    - Phillips, William G. See Container II:27, same heading
    - Reich, David, 1991
    - Rosters and biographical information, 1966-1990, undated, (2 folders)
    - Thomas, Collis, 1992
  - Subject file locations, 1986
  - Survey research See also Container II:28, Questionnaires
    - Constituent mail and casework, 1983
    - Fact Sheet evaluation, 1981
    - DSG Legislative Report delivery, 1980
    - Research services (Box II:35)
      - 1974
      - 1987
    - Role and research services, 1981
      - Members
      - Miscellany
      - Staff, (2 folders)
    - Special Report evaluation
      - 1981
      - 1982 (Box II:36)
    - Upcoming reports, 1980
  - Task force
    - Committees
      - Appropriations, 1971-1972
      - Civil rights, 1969-1972
      - Consumer affairs, 1969-1974
      - Economic and tax policy, 1969-1972
      - Food and agriculture, 1969-1973
      - Foreign affairs, 1971-1974, 1981-1985
      - Health, 1989-1991
      - Health and welfare, 1969-1971, undated
      - International affairs and defense policy, 1969-1971
      - Tax reform See Containers II:166-171, H.R. 4242
      - Women, 1973-1976
    - Organization, 1969-1975, 1982-1983, undated, (3 folders)
  - Tax status, legal review, 1980-1981
- Part II: Chronological File, 1958-1994 (Box II:37-64)
  Research publications, memoranda, notes, and related material.
  Compiled by year, month, and day.
  - 1958-1963, (7 folders) (Box II:37)
  - 1964-1965, (6 folders) (Box II:38)
  - 1966, (4 folders) (Box II:39)
  - 1967
    - Jan.-May, (2 folders)
    - June-Dec., (4 folders) (Box II:40)
  - 1968
    - Jan.-Aug., (3 folders)
    - Sept.-Dec. (Box II:41)
  - 1969
    - Jan.-Oct., (5 folders)
  - 1969 (Box II:42)
    - Nov.-Dec.
  - 1970
    - Jan.-Sept., (6 folders)
    - Oct.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box II:43)
  - 1971, (3 folders)
  - 1972
    - Jan.-May, (2 folders)
    - June-Dec., (6 folders) (Box II:44)
  - 1973
    - Jan.-Apr., (2 folders)
    - May-Dec., (5 folders) (Box II:45)
  - 1974
    - Jan.-Feb.
    - Mar.-Dec., (5 folders) (Box II:46)
  - 1975
    - Jan.-Mar.
    - Apr.-Nov., (6 folders) (Box II:47)
    - Dec. (Box II:48)
  - 1976
    - Jan.-July, (6 folders)
    - Aug.-Dec., (3 folders) (Box II:49)
  - 1977
    - Jan.-Apr., (4 folders)
    - May-Oct., (6 folders) (Box II:50)
    - Nov.-Dec. (Box II:51)
  - 1978
    - Jan.-May, (5 folders)
    - June -Dec., (7 folders) (Box II:52)
  - 1979-1982, (4 folders) (Box II:53)
  - 1983
    - Jan.-Apr., (4 folders)
    - May-Aug., (7 folders) (Box II:54)
    - Sept.-Dec., (7 folders) (Box II:55)
  - 1984
    - Jan., (1 folder)
    - Feb.-May, (6 folders) (Box II:56)
    - June-Sept., (6 folders) (Box II:57)
    - Oct.-Dec., (3 folders) (Box II:58)
  - 1985
    - Jan.-May, (7 folders)
    - June-Sept., (7 folders) (Box II:59)
    - Oct.-Dec., (5 folders) (Box II:60)
  - 1986
    - Mar.-Aug., (3 folders)
    - Sept.-Dec., (5 folders) (Box II:61)
  - 1987
    - Jan.-Feb., (2 folders)
    - Mar.-June, (7 folders) (Box II:62)
    - July-Nov., (8 folders) (Box II:63)
    - Dec., (2 folders) (Box II:64)
  - 1988-1990, (4 folders)
  - 1991-1994, undated
- Part II: Research Publications, 1959-1994 (Box II:65-87)
  Publications prepared for members, indexes, and bibliographies.
  Arranged alphabetically by title of publication, or by document type, and thereunder chronologically.
  - Bibliographies, 1960-1987, (2 folders) (Box II:65)
  - Binders for Special Report, 1983-1985
  - Daily Report
    - 1986-1989, (2 folders)
    - 1994, (2 folders)
  - Executive Summary, 1987-1989, (2 folders)
  - Fact Sheet
    - Indexes, 1960-1967
    - Chronological file (Box II:66)
      - 1959-1964, (2 folders)
      - 1967
      - 1969-1970
      - 1974
      - 1975 (Box II:67)
      - 1977-1980, (3 folders)
      - 1981-1984, (4 folders) (Box II:68)
      - 1985-1989, (3 folders) (Box II:69)
      - 1992-1994, (3 folders) (Box II:70)
  - Issue Report
    - 1972
    - 1974 (Box II:71)
  - DSG Legislative Report
    - 1975, (3 folders)
    - 1979
      - Jan.-June, (2 folders)
      - July-Dec., (5 folders) (Box II:72)
    - 1980
      - Jan.-May, (2 folders)
      - June-Dec., (4 folders) (Box II:73)
    - 1982, (3 folders)
    - 1983-1984, (7 folders) (Box II:74)
    - 1986 (Box II:75)
    - 1992, (5 folders)
    - 1993, (3 folders) (Box II:76)
  - Record Votes, House of Representatives
    - Memoranda, 1972-1986
    - 95th Congress
      - First Session, 1977, (3 folders)
      - Second Session, 1978, (3 folders) (Box II:77)
    - 96th Congress
      - First Session, 1979, (3 folders)
      - Second Session, 1980, (2 folders) (Box II:78)
    - 97th Congress
      - First Session, 1981
      - Second Session, 1982
    - 98th Congress, Second Session, 1984, (2 folders)
    - 99th Congress (Box II:79)
      - First Session, 1985, (2 folders)
      - Second Session, 1986, (2 folders)
    - 100th Congress
      - First Session, 1987, (2 folders)
      - Second Session, 1988, (1 folder) (Box II:80)
    - 101st Congress
      - First Session, 1989, (2 folders)
      - Second Session
        - 1989, (2 folders)
        - 1990, (2 folders)
    - 102nd Congress, First Session, 1991, (4 folders) (Box II:81)
  - Special Report
    - 1970-1977, (3 folders)
    - 1978-1981, (5 folders) (Box II:82)
    - 1982-1984, (5 folders) (Box II:83)
    - 1985-1986, (6 folders) (Box II:84)
    - 1987-1989, (4 folders) (Box II:85)
    - 1990 (Box II:86)
    - 1991-1994, (4 folders)
  - Staff Bulletin, 1975, 1982, (4 folders) (Box II:87)
- Part II: Services and Activities, 1937-1994 (Box II:87-102)
  Political election campaign records, training materials for freshmen orientation, office management, legislative issues, and whip system records.
  - Campaign file (Box II:87)
    - Candidate services, 1969-1971, undated
    - Congressional campaigns
      - 1960
        - Campaign handbook
        - “Truth sheets” (Box II:88)
      - 1962, chronological file
      - 1964
        - Campaign committee, 1963-1964